在2008年金凯瑞的电影《好好先生》中，金扮演了一个生活毫无出路的废柴，
In the 2008 Jim Carrey movie, Yes Man, Jim plays a man whose life is at a dead end,
因此他参加了个人发展计划（真人秀），加入的唯一前提就是：对事情说“好”。
and so he enrolls in a personal development course with a single premise: say yes to things.
无可避免的，他竟很好的断章取义，单纯的对他遇到的
Inevitably he takes it well out of context and simply decides to say yes to every single
每一个机遇和问题都说“好”，
opportunity and question that comes his way,
引导他走向个人转变，拥有一个惊喜的浪漫和充实的生活。
leading him to a personal transformation, a surprise romance, and a fulfilling life.
在【事图秀】的工作有时真的很无聊。我是说，我们做了一些很勤勉的研究，
We here at The Infographics got really bored。I mean, we did some diligent research and
想知道说“好”的力量是如何转化的，
wanted to find out just how transforming the power of Yes really was,
所以我们再一次让观众备受喜爱的实验小白鼠重出囚笼，并给他一个任务：
so once more we let your favorite lab rat out of his cage and tasked him with one job:
一周时间，对任何事情都说“好”.
say yes to everything for an entire week.
第1天：我猜猜，一定是【事图秀】的某个领导怀旧了21世纪，
Day 1: So I'm guessing that somebody over at Infographics got nostalgic for the 2000s
看了电影《好好先生》，然后决定，
and watched Yes Man, then decided,
“嘿，在现实世界里强迫某个人这么做一定很酷”，然后我就来了。
“Hey that'd be cool to force somebody to do in the real world”, and here I am.
我在挑战前看了这部电影，这里有个事实，电影是基于剧本的，
I watched the movie before this challenge started, and here's the thing, the movie is based on a script,
编剧在剧本可以塑造故事，让金凯瑞对一切
where the writers can shape the story to make the consequences of Jim
说“好”的结果是他们想要的。
Carrey's saying yes to everything be whatever they want it to be.
影片最后金凯瑞开始了全新的生活，与美丽的佐伊（Zooey Deschanel）存在着
Jim Carrey ends up with a brand new life and a wonderful relationship with the beautiful
一段完美的关系，然而在现实世界对一切说“好”，
Zooey Deschanel, in the real world me saying yes to everything could very well
到最后我可能会变成一个帮墨西哥黑帮运毒的骡子。
end up with me becoming a drug mule for the Mexican Mafia.
不确定性强于任何挑战，这是唯一我觉得有真正的威胁让我陷入严重的麻烦，
Morseso than any challenge, this one I feel has the real potential to get me in serious trouble,
愚蠢的我当然，要去做了。
and stupid me is of course, going to do it.
规则很简单：对遇到的每一个机会和每一个提议都说“好”。
Rules are simple: say yes to every opportunity and every offer that comes my way.
像一个积极向上的禅师一样生活一周，不抵触世间天地万物
Live my life like a positive, life-affirming zen master for a whole week, and say yes to the universe.
以下是我生活、苦笑，友爱的一周，就像一个25岁左右的大学毕业生
This is my week to Live, Laugh, Love, like a mid-twenties college grad going through
经历她的第一次多重存在主义危机。
her first of multiple existential crisis.
顺便提一句，我刚意识到有了这个挑战，我将正式完成
By the way, I just realized that with this challenge I'll officially have lived out the
两部金凯瑞电影的情节。你能猜出另一部吗？
plot of two Jim Carrey movies. can you guess which one is the other?
第3天：前七十二个小时下来，一切都一团糟。
Day 3: First seventy two hours down, and what a mess things have been.
我没有告诉女朋友这个挑战，因为没有人比她更能承担
I didn't tell the girlfriend about the challenge, because there is no one who could handle the
我只能说“好”的后果。
responsibility of me being able to say only yes worse than her.
我甚至不想去想，如果她知道我对她的每一个愿望和欲望只能说“好”的话，
I don't even want to think what kind of terrible, ridiculous things she would rope me into doing
她会逼迫我做出什么可怕、荒谬的事情。
if she knew I could only say yes to her every wish and desire.
举个例子，她一直想和一对夫妇参加一个神秘谋杀晚宴，
For example, she's been wanting to do this murder mystery dinner party thing with another couple,
而这对夫妇是非常糟糕的。
and these two are the absolute worst.
他们浮夸到了极点，任何时间对任何事物都有极强的控制欲，
They are both over dramatic to the extreme and have to be in charge of everything all the time
说句实话，我都不知道女友是怎么和他们做成朋友的，
honestly, I have no idea why she's friends with them,
但和他们在一起的一晚就如同是钳子拔牙。
but an evening with themis like pulling your teeth out with a pair of pliers.
对了，他们还喜欢一有机会就进行极端的PDA活动。
Oh, and they love to engage in extreme PDA at the drop of a hat.
不了，谢谢您了。我告诉女友我不介意参加神秘谋杀晚宴，
No thank you, I told her that I don't mind doing murder mystery dinner party,
但绝对不和他们一起，并且基本每隔一周我就要拒绝一次。
but absolutely not with them, and have been refusing an invitation just about every other week.
不存在的！
NOT HAPPENING.
然后，我的第一天相对安然无恙，至少在女友回家之前。
So, my first day was relatively uneventful, at least until the girlfriend got home.
他们刚在我们这条街上建了一个全新的蔬菜烧烤店，
They just built a brand new Veggie Grill down the street from us,
对不了解的人说，就是一家素食餐厅，他们只供应蔬菜。
and for those of you who don't know, it's a vegetarian restaurant where they serve only vegetables.
自从施工以来，女友就一直关注着这家餐厅，每次被她提起，
She's been eyeballing it ever since they started construction and every time she brought it up
我都设法转移话题，但这次她又问了一次，我尽职地说，“好的”
I managed to sidestep the conversation, but this time she asked again and I dutifully
我发誓刚说出这句话的时候身体抽搐了一下，她只是坐在那里，
I swear I physically winced as the words left my mouth and she just kind of sat there
然后说，“哇，真的嘛，这么简单？”。
for a moment and said, “Wow, really, just like that?”
我内心一边万马奔腾，一边点点头，然后我们就去了蔬菜烧烤店。
And I silently nodded while screaming inside, and off to Veggie Grill we went.
老实说，还没那么糟，假鸡块吃起来还不错，
Honestly, it's not that bad, their fake chicken nuggets even tasted kind of alright, but it's
但就是这样...没有吃到真实的肉让人难过的心碎。
always just so... heartbreakingly disappointing to not be eating the real thing.
让人感觉不到满足。
And it never fills me up.
好吧，第二天开始有些奇怪。
Ok, so day two was a little weird.
这次我们一起去了杂货店，她建议我们买一些
This time we went to the grocery store together and she suggested we pick up several things
让我畏缩的东西。
that made me cringe hard.
一些带有“全有机”和“益生菌”标签的东西。
Things with labels like “all organic” and “pro-biotic”.
她说，“这些杏子、菠菜和纸板汁对健康很有益，
“This apricot, spinach and cardboard juice would be really healthy for you,
你应该拿上这些而不是些肥宅快乐水”。“好的，亲爱的” ，我尽职尽责的回答。
you should pick that up instead of some soda.”, she said, and “Yes, dear.” I dutifully replied.
“你为什么不试试这种藜麦的无可可豆、无糖巧克力，
“Why don't you try this quinoa based cocoa-free, sugar-free chocolate
用回收的有机鱼骨和和“悲剧”做成的，而不是那个奇巧巧克力棒？”
made out of recycled organic fish bones and sadness instead of that Kit Kat bar?”
“好的，当然”
“Yes, sure”
“我们应该得到一些健康的冰淇淋，而不是奥利奥饼干和奶油，
“We should get some of this healthy ice cream instead of that oreo cookies and cream.
它的成分有羽衣甘蓝，山羊奶，喜马拉雅海盐和‘抑郁’”
It's made out of kale, goat milk, himalayan sea salt and depression.”
“好的，听起来不错。”
“Yes, sounds great.”
就这样来来去去，现在的厨房里装满了带有各种意图的食品，
On and on it went, and now my kitchen is full of food that for all intents and purposes,
几乎全都不能吃。
is pretty much inedible.
别误会我的意思，我知道垃圾食品是，垃圾，但我和她之间
Don't get me wrong, I know junk food is, well, junk, but there has always existed a balance
总是有一种平衡，她在我们的饮食中占据了健康纯粹的一半，
between her and I, she gets to health nazi half of our diet, and I get to stay sane by
而我偶尔也会放纵另一半，以保持理智。
occasionally indulging the other half of the time.
现在这种平衡被破坏了，而我下个星期将享受“零餐”。
Now that balance is destroyed, and I'm going to enjoy exactly zero of my meals for the next week.
谢谢你全家，【事图秀】。
Thanks, Infographics.
然而，这并不是那天最奇怪的事情。
That however wasn't the weirdness of the day.
奇怪发生在结账的时候。
The weirdness would come at checkout time.
在购物时，我总是会随身带一两个可重复使用的袋子，这比较环保，
I always take a reusable bag or two with me when we go shopping, it's environmentally friendly
在加利福尼亚，超市还对塑料袋收费，想要阻止人们
and in California they also charge for plastic bags in an attempt to deter you
使用塑料袋并将其扔掉，因为它们最终有可能落入大海并杀死海龟。
from using them and throwing them away so they end up in the ocean and murder sea turtles.
所以我随身带了两个可重复使用的袋子，明显的我已经准备好把我们的
So I had the two reusable bags with me, and I very clearly was ready to put our groceries
杂物放进环保袋了，但当收银台的女孩问我，“你需要塑料袋吗？”。
inside of them, when the checkout girl asked me, “Would you like plastic bags for these?”.
我立刻就答应了，因为你知道，我是一个白痴，选择了这个作为职业，
I immediately said yes, because you know, I'm an idiot who chose this as a career, and
然后我不得不沙雕地拿着我的塑料袋兜着的杂货，
then had to very stupidly take my plastic-bagged groceries while holding
同时拿着我那环保袋。
my reusable bags in my hand.
事情发生时女朋友没有注意，但当她转过身来时，
The girlfriend wasn't paying attention when it happened, but when she turned around
她给了我一个非常严厉的“wtf”表情，我只是耸耸肩，
she gave me a very stern 'wtf' look, and I just shrugged my shoulders
说也许我们可以用它们来当作垃圾袋。
and said maybe we can use them for trash bags.
然后我们走出了商店，如果她之前没有怀疑哪点出错了，
Then we walked out of the store, and if she didn't suspect something was up before, she
她现在肯定有。
definitely did now.
不出所料，我们一走出商店，就被一个拿着写字板的人拦住了。
Predictably as soon as we walked out of the store we got stopped by a guy with a clipboard.
你知道的那种类型。
you know the type.
我通常会躲开这些请愿者，就像一个美国橄榄球联盟（NFL）在他赢得比赛
I typically outmaneuver these petitioners like an NFL running back on his way to scoring
触地得分的途中来回跑一样，但这家伙很不人道，
a game-winning touchdown, but this guy was inhuman,
他将自己传送到了我们身前，没有人能避开他。
he practically teleported in front of us and there was no avoiding him.
他想要我们签字，以示我们对联邦政府强迫加州
He wanted us to sign to show our support against the federal government forcing California
降低汽车油耗标准的反对。
to lower its gas mileage standards for vehicles.
尽职尽责，我答应了。
Dutifully, I said yes.
女友此时眯起了眼，
The girlfriend's eyes narrowed at this point,
她知道我特意对任何有实质原因的活动都不表示公开支持，
she knows I go out of my way to not show public support for any specific causes,
而倾向于私底下的支持。
preferring to keep my support private.
我不喜欢群体，我也不喜欢在公开场合把自己和任何特定群体在意识形态排成一列。
I don't like groups, and I don't like lining myself up ideologically in public with any specific groups.
这样很容易陷入非自己本身的价值观，
it's too easy to get caught up in values that aren't your own,
或让群体展示你不同意的价值观，但现在突然所有人都认为你认同 。
or to have the group show values that you disagree with but now suddenly everyone thinks you identify with.
你只是无法控制一个团体的走向，或者他们带给你的标签。
You just can't control a group, or how they'll make you look.
不，谢谢。
No thank you.
哪里出事了，她无疑对自己想。
Something was up, she no doubt thought to herself.
然而，那个请愿人又丢下一颗重磅炸弹，老实说，
Then though, the petitioner dropped a bomb, and I honestly think
我现在就想变成一千个太阳灼烧掉这个男人。
I hate this man now with all the fury of a thousand suns.
“你想在几天内和我们一起在市中心举行抗议活动吗？”
“Would you like to join us in a protest downtown in a few days?”
是的，我绝对希望100％做到这一点，我咬紧牙关紧绷。
WHY YES I'D LOVE TO ABSOLUTELY 100% DO EXACTLY THAT -I growled through clenched teeth.
他不知道自己刚刚离死亡有多远，也不知道此刻我内心燃烧着
Unaware of how close to death this man had just come, or of the fiery furnace of wrath
熊熊怒火，他兴奋地记下了我的电话号码，
burning inside me at the moment, he excitedly took my phone number down
以便他们的协调员在周末晚些时候给我打电话并告诉我详细安排。
so their coordinator could call me with details later in the week.
瞧，我现在成为了一个团体的一员，在休假的日子里公开抗议。
And voila, just like that I'd now be protesting in public on one of my days off, as part of a group.
一群狂热粉。
Fan-freaking-tastic.
当我们到了车上，女朋友笑得合不拢嘴。
When we got to the car, the girlfriend grinned from ear to ear.
“你不能说不”，她说，一个逐渐变态的微笑洋溢在她的脸上。
“You can't say no”, she said, a very disturbingly conniving smile spreading across her face.
我解释道，准确的说，在余下的五天我不得不继续对所有事情说“好”就对了，
I explained that it would be more accurate to say that I had to say yes to everything for another five days,
我发誓，当她毫无疑问地策划了上千个计划和阴谋时，我看到了她眼中的恶魔，
and I swear I saw the devil in her eyes as she no doubt hatched a thousand schemes and plots,
她简直兴奋得头晕目眩，现在能让我做些什么呢！
practically giddy with excitement over what she could get me to do now.
第7天：
Day 7:
完成。
Ok.
挑战结束。
Challenge over.
再也不想再来一次了。
Never repeating again.
在《好好先生》中，金凯瑞仅靠说“好”就遇到了转折，获得了心上人。
In Yes Man, Jim Carrey had his life turned around and got the girl all by saying yes to life.
在我的现实生活，我被勒索到女朋友能从我身上得到
In my real life I've been blackmailed into every possible concession the girlfriend could
的每一个可能的让步，并且再一次，公开地羞辱了我。
get out of me and was once more, very publicly humiliated.
让我们回到开头。
Let me start at the beginning.
没过多久，女朋友就开始滥用她的权力，
It didn't take long for the girlfriend to start abusing her power to make me say yes
让我对一切都说是。
to everything.
背部按摩？
Back rub?
好的。
Yes.
脚部按摩？
Foot rub?
好的。
Yes.
来一杯冰水？
Fetch a glass of ice water?
马上！！
Yes.
我累了，你能再次遛下狗吗？
I'm tired, can you take the dog out again?
可以。
Yes.
可以预见，我基本上成为了一个奴隶，尽管值得赞扬的是，她在第一天仅使用这种方式滥用了它，
Predictably, I basically became a slave. although to her credit she only abused it in this fashion
我想我不能太责怪她。
for the first day, and I suppose I can't blame her too much for it.
我的意思是，想象一下，你可以让某人为你做一个星期的突发奇想，
I mean imagine you could get someone to do your whim for a whole week,
如果我对她的克制印象深刻的话。
if anything I'm impressed by her restraint.
然而，她不可避免的想起现在可以让我参加每个社交活动，
However, she inevitably remembered that she could now get me to go to every social engagement
那些我每次都死去活来不愿意去的活动，那么猜猜这周谁要去宝宝送礼会，
I have fought her tooth and nail on since forever, so guess who got to go to a baby
然后去为她一个朋友的8岁儿子开生日派对？
shower and then a birthday party for the 8 year old son of one of her friends this week?
真的不是孩子的粉。
I don't really do children.
直到最近，我才意识到有一天我们会有一个属于自己的孩子，
It's only been recently that I've warmed up to the idea of having one of our own one day,
老实说，在内心深处，我喜欢和她生孩子的想法。
and to be honest deep down inside I love the thought of having a child with her.
但是其他人的孩子...哦，算了吧。
But other people's kids... oh god no.
什么都行，除了孩子。
Anything but that.
我在孩子傍边感觉即奇怪又尴尬。
I'm weird and awkward around children.
我曾不得不给三个不同的朋友发短信，问他们你是如何向
I once had to text three different friends asking them how do you introduce yourself
一个十岁的孩子介绍自己的。 你是不是，和他们们碰碰拳头或者什么的？
to a ten year old. do you just like, give them a handshake or something?
所以我不得不坐在一个一堆大吼大叫的孩子们的生日派对上，
So I got to sit through a birthday party full of screaming children
完全不知道如何与他们恰当地互动。
whom I had no idea how to properly interact with.
真的我对孩子一无所知，就像他们在八岁的时候就知道如何分辨面孔了吗？
Like I know nothing about children, do they even know how to tell faces apart yet at eight years old?
然后是宝宝送礼会，我不得不和另外两个被胁迫的丈夫/男朋友
Then there was the baby shower, where I had to sit quietly with the two other husbands/boyfriends
安静地坐在一起，而女人们则在各种与婴儿有关的礼物上“啧啧”和“啊哈”。
who got roped into going while the women all 'oohed' and 'aahed' at various baby-related gifts.
我甚至不知道我们该带什么礼物，我建议买个搅拌机，
I didn't even know what gift we should bring, I suggested a blender
因为我完全不清楚婴儿食品是怎么进行的，女朋友则是摇摇头，
because I'm not entirely sure how baby food works, and the girlfriend just shook her head
然后拖着我去熊宝宝商店。
and dragged me shopping for Baby Bjorns.
不过，本周的真正大奖是，我知道，就是知道，这事会发生，
The real prize of the week though, and I knew, just knew, that this would happen, which is
这也是为什么我一开始没有告诉女朋友这个挑战…
why I didn't tell the girlfriend about the challenge in the first place...
我打赌你们大多数人都能猜到。
I bet most of you can guess.
是的，与“过于戏精-超级专横-过度亲热-不合时宜”夫妇一起参与神秘谋杀晚宴，
Yep, murder mystery dinner with Mr. and Mrs. overly-dramatic-super-bossy-very-publicly-inappropriate-PDA.
噢，那是一个时代主题晚宴，所以我们必须穿服装并扮演角色。
Oh and it was period themed so of course we had to wear costumes and act the part.
戏精夫妇喜欢的类型。
Which Mr. and Mrs. overly-dramatic absolutely loved.
规则是这样的：我们随机从帽子里抽取角色，
So the way it worked was like this: we showed up, randomly pulled roles out of a hat, and
然后穿上符合我们这个时期的角色的服装。
then got dressed in our period appropriate costumes.
我抽到到了一个军官的角色，这让我有点略微吃惊，
I got the role of an army officer, which was kind of on-the-nose to be honest,
但女友得到了情妇的角色，当她大声朗读出自己的角色时，我不禁大笑起来。
but the girlfriend got the role of mistress, and I could not stop laughing when she read it aloud.
我开始在晚上称呼她为“荡妇”，为此她每次都会捶我，
I proceeded to call her 'wench' for the evening and my arms are bruised badly from all the
所以我的手臂变得青肿。你们有些人知道的，她经常练拳击，
times she punched me for calling her wench. as some of you know, she boxes regularly,
“荡妇”是一个她讨厌的刺戳。
so she's got a nasty jab.
戏精夫抽到了警察局长，戏精妇抽到了有抱负的新星。
Mr. and Mrs. overly-dramatic though, well he pulled police chief, and she got aspiring starlet.
我已有预感今晚将是人类历史上最痛苦、
Already I could tell the evening was going to be the single most painful, unbearable
最难以忍受的一次体验。
experience in human history.
所以你应该在他们给你上不同菜的时候好好地坐下来，
So you're supposed to sit for dinner while they serve you different courses, and right
然后从晚宴开始后戏精夫妇将会忽视你，
from the get-go Mr. and Mrs. Drama would steadfastly refuse to acknowledge you
除非你用他们虚构的人物名来称呼他们。
unless you addressed them by their fictional character names.
对了，他们还要求我们围着桌子，
Oh, and they demanded we go around the table
为自己的角色编造背景故事并进行自我介绍。
and make up backstories for our character and introduce ourselves.
并且他们也会不断对每个人的故事背景提出有用的、非常有力的“建议”，
Except they would insist on making helpful and very forceful 'suggestions' to every single person's backstory,
你知道，一些小提示可以增强“沉浸感”。
you know, little notes to enhance the 'immersion'.
我真的认为我磨牙打碎了一颗臼齿。
I honestly think I shattered a molar from grinding my teeth.
到了晚上才十分钟，他们已经想试图控制每个人的体验。
It was barely ten minutes into the evening and already they were trying to control everybody's experience.
关于这种古老谋杀神秘事件，有一条不成文的规定，
There's an unwritten rule about these old-timey murder mystery dinner events
每个人都会因为某种原因而带上英国口音。
where everyone for some reason puts on a british accent.
因为每次出现神秘谋杀案的时候，那就和英国人有关。
the moment you think murder mystery, everyone thinks british.
真的很奇怪。
It's really weird.
所以很自然地，我就用我能应付的最难听的澳大利亚口音解释说
So naturally I put on the most awful australian accent I could manage, explained that I was
我是一名来自“下乌达”的军官，并称所有人为“伙计”，
an officer from 'down undah', and called everyone mate.
除了我所谓的“荡妇”女友，
except the girlfriend whom I referred to exclusively as wench,
作为回报每次她都会打我一下。
receiving a swift punch in the arm in return every time.
长话短说，在第一个菜进行到一半时，
To make a very painful and long story short, halfway through the first course the lights
灯光熄灭一切进入黑暗，出现了一声假枪声，有人开始尖叫，
go out and everything is pitch black, there's a fake gunshot and someone screams,
当灯光再次亮起，庄园的主人则死于枪伤。
and when the lights come back up the lord of the manor is dead from a gunshot wound.
然后，你需要找出凶手是谁，因为当你绘制角色时，
Then you're supposed to figure out who did it because secretly when you drew for characters,
纸条上写者你是否是杀人犯。
your slip says if you were the murderer or not.
还有一把要藏起来的道具枪
And you get a prop gun to hide.
我敢肯定，对于其他任何一组玩家来说，这都可能是一场爆炸，
I'm sure with any other group of people, it could've been a blast, but right from the
但从一开始就是戏精夫妇负责安排场景，当然他们安排了，他毕竟抽中了警察局长的身份。
start Mr. and Mrs. drama took charge, and of course they did, he did pull chief of police after all.
然后，我们花了大约一个小时的时间和这两个戏精来回盘问人们的背景，
Then we spent about an hour with those two going back and forth grilling people's backstories
并且在我们面前有意无意的勾勾搭搭，
and randomly making out with each other for no reason in front of us,
所有的这些时候，我都只管吃我的食物。
all while I tried to just eat my food.
好不容易到的上甜点的时刻，说真的，这种时候服务太拖沓了，
After struggling to make it to dessert, seriously, they serve you so damn slowly at these things.
我终于宣布，既然庄园主以前是海军军官
I finally announced that since the lord of the manor had previously been an officer in the navy,
而我作为英国皇家海军唯一的军官，正式宣布
and as the only officer from Her Majesty's royal navy, I was officially declaring
这项调查事关国家安全，然后指责那个“荡妇”，
the investigation a matter of national security, and then blamed the wench,
【又打我一下】，指控她谋杀。
who punched me for calling her that, and charged her with murder.
她抗议，其他人也抗议，我告诉他们，
She protested, as did the rest of the room, and I told them that this was 19th century
这是19世纪的英国， 显然作为一名军官，我可以没有任何证据的责怪任何非贵族的人,
Britain, apparently, and as a military officer I could literally blame anyone who wasn't
并且也没有人敢出来质疑我。
noble with no evidence and nobody would dare question me.
然后我说我需要带走那个“荡妇”，【再次打我】，来一个非常私人和热切的搜索，
I then said I needed to take the wench, punched me again, for a very private and intense search
去找到她身上的凶器，不管它藏在哪里。
to find the murder weapon on her person, no matter where it may be hidden
她再次打我一拳，这次是因为恶心。
to which she punched me again, this time for being gross.
事实证明，她确实是杀手。
Turns out though, she really was the killer.
当然，这需要花半个小时的来回与戏精夫妇
Of course it took a half hour of back and forth with Mr. and Mrs. Drama boss dictating
口述整件事，当然他们应该在第一时间就让我脱衣搜查我的女朋友.
the whole thing, when they should've just let me strip search my wench girlfriend in the first place.
如果这还不够我受的话，到第二天我就得去参加我承诺过的抗议活动。
If that wasn't enough, the next day I had to show up at the protest I had promised to attend.
你猜怎么着？组织者只邀请到六个人来参加，
And guess what? the organizers had only gotten like half a dozen people to show up, so I
所以我只好在洛杉矶市中心举着牌子游行，另外五个人则随意的喊着口号。
got to march around downtown Los Angeles holding a sign up with five other people chanting random slogans.
在生活，尤其是对一段感情，
In life, and especially in a relationship,
有时对你不想做的事情妥协并答应是很重要的。
it's important to compromise and say yes sometimes to things you don't want to do.
当你同意别人想做或喜欢做的事情时，会让别人感到高兴，
It makes other people happy when you agree to things they want to do or they like to
即使自己本身不喜欢，不想做，
do even if you don't like or want to do those things.
妥协基本上是快乐友谊或甜蜜关系的秘诀。
Compromise is basically the secret to a happy friendship, or a happy relationship.
本周，我做了足够多的妥协来维持我接下来几年的生活，
This week though, I did enough compromising to last me the next several years,
如果再有人拿着请愿书在我离开商店时向我走来的话，
and if anyone comes up to me when I'm exiting the store with a petition in hand,
我就是李小龙，直接削他们的脸，然后在他们反应过来之前跑掉。
I'm karate, chopping them in the face and running away before they can recover.
你能一周之内说“好”吗？
Think you could say only yes for a whole week?
你还想看到备受宠爱的小白鼠进行哪些挑战？
What other challenges do you want to see your favorite guinea pig undertake?
写在评论中让我们知道吧！
Let us know in the comments!
与往常一样，如果你喜欢这个视频，别忘了喜欢，分享和订阅更多很棒的内容！
And as always if you enjoyed this video don't forget to Like, Share, and Subscribe for more great content!